<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_27196_16905420"> 
<user id ="MS_130908655"> 
	 <username>dysLEXIc™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>LARGO</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1166425800</date> 
 <body>I never saw the original. but the remake was alright.    I don't know why, but I find it hard to believe that shit really happened. just my opinion though....</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27196_16906016"> 
<user id ="MS_470580"> 
	 <username>carnival boy</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Highlands</city> 
	 <province>Scotland</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1166427300</date> 
 <body>I'd like to think that I'm pretty open minded and I'm not going to say that something like that COULDN'T happen. But did anyone see the documentary that they made about the real Amityville story? Seemed like a bunch of crap to me.    For the movie, I prefer the original.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27196_16906537"> 
<user id ="MS_130908655"> 
	 <username>dysLEXIc™</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>LARGO</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1166428380</date> 
 <body>    yeah I mean hauntings really DO happen. but I've heard people say that the basement in the amity house is suppossedly the gateway to hell. and the movie made it look so fictional. I don't think that I'm 100% right, but it just seemed unrealistic to me though..</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27196_16907221"> 
<user id ="MS_126024385"> 
	 <username>Misfit Films</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>Nova Scotia</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1166429640</date> 
 <body>I thought the remake was better. It didn't just focus on the haunting of a house. It also focused on one of the family members losing his sanity from mere thoughts coming from the house. The original I found was crap.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27196_16907942"> 
<user id ="MS_470580"> 
	 <username>carnival boy</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Highlands</city> 
	 <province>Scotland</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1166431020</date> 
 <body>    You should try and watch the documentary. It's called The Real Amityville Horror. It was made for channel 4 here in the UK. It's interesting to see all sides of the story. When the family moved into the house, even though it was cheap after the murders, they'd taken on a much higher mortgage than they could afford and the father's business was failing. The guy that murdered his family in the house, Ronald DeFeo, it was his defence attorney that met with the Lutz family, and soon afterwards they came out with the story of the haunting, hoping that it would get DeFeo a retrial. And making the Lutzs quite a bit of money. The guy that wrote the book apparently never cared if the story was true or not. All all further residents of the house have reported nothing unusual.    It would be sad if it was all a hoax.    But it does make for a good story :)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27196_16908207"> 
<user id ="MS_108699070"> 
	 <username>~*~Jennifer~*~</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Scotland</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1166431500</date> 
 <body>    i saw that doc when it was on =) & i agree, it would be sad if it was a hoax & it is a good story....i believe in hauntings etc myself even if this one isn't real =p    as for the movie, i saw the remake & it was ok....not very realistic at all but quite entertaining =P</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27196_16910612"> 
<user id ="MS_4831961"> 
	 <username>Emily</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>AUBURN</city> 
	 <province>Alabama</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1166436240</date> 
 <body>Am I the only person that thought both version were wretched?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27196_16910712"> 
<user id ="MS_470580"> 
	 <username>carnival boy</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>Highlands</city> 
	 <province>Scotland</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1166436420</date> 
 <body>    Probably not, no. They're not great movies by any stretch of the imagination. But the original is worth a watch, and I do have a taste for bad horror movies.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27196_16911671"> 
<user id ="MS_4831961"> 
	 <username>Emily</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>AUBURN</city> 
	 <province>Alabama</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1166438160</date> 
 <body>    I just found the original to be really, really boring.      But it did spawn a ton of cheesy, semi-entertaining sequels. It certainly belongs in the 70s kitsch horror genre.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_27196_16919778"> 
<user id ="MS_322380"> 
	 <username>floyd</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>milford</city> 
	 <province>New Jersey</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1166453160</date> 
 <body>    nah, neither are very good.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>