<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39670314"> 
<user id ="MS_12051898"> 
	 <username>Nory</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>U really wanna know?</city> 
	 <province>MARYLAND</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205354340</date> 
 <body>  he's saying this affects the quality of his products...  this is why visa sucks</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39670624"> 
<user id ="MS_595868"> 
	 <username>the grand facade so soon will burn</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>East Los Angeles</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205354760</date> 
 <body>The argument can be extended to low-wage migrant farm workers from Mexico and other Latin American countries. For each productive day of their labor, many white-collar professionals have jobs in sales/marketing/logistics, and have cheap produce to enjoy.  It does sound a bit harsh, but consider that I'm a supporter of not only liberated immigration policies but also the enhanced right to form workers union, along with being a supporter of the efforts of leaders such as Caesar Chavez and others who work to increase the earnings of migrant workers.  Every day I thank a low-wage earner for my relatively easy (by comparison) white collar job.  I'd take a slight pay cut to see that these workers earned a little bit more.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39670713"> 
<user id ="MS_12051898"> 
	 <username>Nory</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>U really wanna know?</city> 
	 <province>MARYLAND</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205354880</date> 
 <body>  Chavez didnt like illegal immigration becuz it ruined wages...  come again</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39670806"> 
<user id ="MS_595868"> 
	 <username>the grand facade so soon will burn</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>East Los Angeles</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205354940</date> 
 <body>Streamlining the immigration process is key - and reaching the understanding that no human being is "illegal" by nature (one of my favorite Kucinich quotes from the Democratic debates).</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39672473"> 
<user id ="MS_154436164"> 
	 <username>Stupendous Friend</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>40</age> 
	 <city>SFofAmerica</city> 
	 <province>Washington DC</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205357400</date> 
 <body>Biggest bunch of Bullshit!  You need to watch Pirates of Silicon Valley, where Bill Gates and Steve Jobs lifted Xerox developed technology for the first PCs with a mouse!  Then Bill pissed off programmers who had been developing and sharing code programming, by copyrighting it and stealing it as easily as he had been handed the technology that Xerox developed, simply because Xerox saw no value in a personal PC back in the 70s, and let Apple Develop their Technology, and then Bill Gates started copyrighting the code for Microsoft just changing it slightly when he had been paid to develop it for Apple, but Steve Jobs didn't listen when Bill told him he should be copyrighting software not just hardware.  The real story is Microsoft doesn't want to pay the wages American's need, and its easy to not have to pay taxes for medicaid and social security for American workers, nor give them the living wage they ask for.  I worked for DELL for 8 months and saw the game.  When I joined their 24/7 technical support through their temp agency Spherion, they told me day one, "It takes us $13 dollars a call to pay you, verses $5 to someone in India."  They used American's for 8 months, and at first we weren't using their decision tree, we were just fixing computers and notating the account, then they came and demanded that we use their decision tree on their software database.  The reason why?  Because it had steps you were to follow to fix a PC, but if you encountered a problem that wasn't in the decision tree, you could put in your solution that you knew or found through research.  Then it was peer reviewed by other Dell Techs who already had a foot in the door.  If they approved your fix for the software or hardware problem, it then got added to the decision tree database.  This in turn was given to Indians without PCs on a script to read from.  It's why so many DELL customer's got pissed with DELL and left them.  They got tired of Indians hanging up on them, because if a problem went off the page, they didn't have the brain power or internet resources to research the problem.  Over in India they were simply hiring fisherman and farmers to read scripts over the telephone who could barely speak English.  I came in with a class of nearly 40 people, of which 22 made it out of training to the job.  Over the 8 months, I watched worker after worker leave, some of them intimidated and run off.  There were only 2 of us left at the end of 8 months, and when I came in for an interview, they refused to hire me and lied saying "I had a problem with management."  I never mentioned one of the 4 different DELL managers in my interview, but one of the 2 Managers I never worked for who interviewed me, lied on their exit interview review of me, and I only found out because the Spherion rep accidentally leaked the information on my exit interview with Spherion.  With Microsoft, they are just one level up.  They can hire like DELL a person in India and pay them 2/3rds less than their American counterpart, and they are not restricted by American 12 hour work rules.  It was a Federal Crime if Dell worked an American more than 12 hours, but not so in India!  Microsoft will end up making General Motors, Ford, (Detroit) etc, problem in the automotive Industry with their software industry.  Detroit began to outsource American jobs, and soon foreign investors such as Toyota and Nissan came in and hired their old work force they laid off, and now look at American Motor Companies 30 years later, on the verge of dying!  America still has some of the hardest and smartest working people right here at home, and every American company that doesn't invest in them, is digging their own grave!  I never bought a DELL before working for the company, and to this day I'll never buy a DELL.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39804031"> 
<user id ="MS_595868"> 
	 <username>the grand facade so soon will burn</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>East Los Angeles</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205568480</date> 
 <body>Canada clearly has the right idea.  Now if Americans can realize that both highly-educated tech and medical workers and lower-educated agriculture and construction workers immigrating from foreign countries is a boon to our economy:  <!-- date/author end --><!-- article start --><table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%"> <tbody> <tr> <td align="center" valign="top" .."font-size: 10px">   View larger image   </td> <td></td> <td width="99%" valign="top" .."font-size: 14px">A record 429,649 foreigners came to live in Canada last year, the interior ministry said Friday, claiming the success of the government's program to bring in immigrants to address  labor shortages.  "These numbers show that our immigration program is responding to Canada's needs, particularly our economic needs," said immigration minister Diane Finley.  But the opposition liberals accused the government of inflating the figures with  temporary workers and students. According to the ministry, almost 30 percent of those admitted to the country in 2007, some 178,000 people, came on a temporary basis. More than 251,000 permanent residency permits were issued in 2007, within the  target range of 240,000 and 265,000, the ministry added.  The figures were released as the conservative government announced plans to "speed up the processing of permanent resident applications, ensuring shorter wait times and making Canada's immigration system more competitive."   More than 900,000 foreigners are currently waiting for the immigration ministry to process their applications to come to Canada. Some have been waiting up to six years, conservative lawmaker Paul Forseth admitted to parliament.  But opposition lawmaker David McGuinty charged that the new plans -- on which no details were given -- were intended to "considerably reduce the number of newcomers." He also said Friday's "falsely inflated" figures were trying to distract from that.  </td> </tr> </tbody></table> I did catch some major lullz when I read of the conservative government's possible inflation of immigration numbes by including temporary workers and students.  Reminded me of George W Bush's decision to label "burger flipping" jobs as belonging to the "manufacturing" sector.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39805124"> 
<user id ="MS_5269567"> 
	 <username>It Don't Mean Much, These Seats are Cheap.</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>Thornton</city> 
	 <province>Colorado</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205570760</date> 
 <body>  Um...he's right.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39805215"> 
<user id ="MS_217129174"> 
	 <username>Chris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>95</age> 
	 <city>London</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205570940</date> 
 <body>  He's got a good point. At least he knows a lot more than everyone here...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39811351"> 
<user id ="MS_238935762"> 
	 <username>The Ogre.</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>68</age> 
	 <city>GREEN BAY</city> 
	 <province>Wisconsin</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205581200</date> 
 <body>So basically, he's saying what? That he can't hire people in this country to do with the jobs? Even with the tech visa program? Bullshit. And those support jobs? Guess where they're going? Yup, to India. He may hire tech support people, but they're in a support center in India. Either taht or they are temporary contract workers.  You did realize that he is the reason that companies won't keep a temp worker past a certain time, right? Because gates fired all his hourly non-exempt staff, then hired them back as contract workers? He kept them for years as contract workers. The only difference was that now, he didn' t have to pay benefits or give them the stock options that he had promised them when he hired them as regular workers. The workers sued and won.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39811391"> 
<user id ="MS_238935762"> 
	 <username>The Ogre.</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>68</age> 
	 <city>GREEN BAY</city> 
	 <province>Wisconsin</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205581200</date> 
 <body>  Bullshit. Why can't they hire americans for those jobs?</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>