<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39804031"> 
<user id ="MS_595868"> 
	 <username>the grand facade so soon will burn</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>East Los Angeles</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205568480</date> 
 <body>Canada clearly has the right idea.  Now if Americans can realize that both highly-educated tech and medical workers and lower-educated agriculture and construction workers immigrating from foreign countries is a boon to our economy:  <!-- date/author end --><!-- article start --><table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%"> <tbody> <tr> <td align="center" valign="top" .."font-size: 10px">   View larger image   </td> <td></td> <td width="99%" valign="top" .."font-size: 14px">A record 429,649 foreigners came to live in Canada last year, the interior ministry said Friday, claiming the success of the government's program to bring in immigrants to address  labor shortages.  "These numbers show that our immigration program is responding to Canada's needs, particularly our economic needs," said immigration minister Diane Finley.  But the opposition liberals accused the government of inflating the figures with  temporary workers and students. According to the ministry, almost 30 percent of those admitted to the country in 2007, some 178,000 people, came on a temporary basis. More than 251,000 permanent residency permits were issued in 2007, within the  target range of 240,000 and 265,000, the ministry added.  The figures were released as the conservative government announced plans to "speed up the processing of permanent resident applications, ensuring shorter wait times and making Canada's immigration system more competitive."   More than 900,000 foreigners are currently waiting for the immigration ministry to process their applications to come to Canada. Some have been waiting up to six years, conservative lawmaker Paul Forseth admitted to parliament.  But opposition lawmaker David McGuinty charged that the new plans -- on which no details were given -- were intended to "considerably reduce the number of newcomers." He also said Friday's "falsely inflated" figures were trying to distract from that.  </td> </tr> </tbody></table> I did catch some major lullz when I read of the conservative government's possible inflation of immigration numbes by including temporary workers and students.  Reminded me of George W Bush's decision to label "burger flipping" jobs as belonging to the "manufacturing" sector.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39805124"> 
<user id ="MS_5269567"> 
	 <username>It Don't Mean Much, These Seats are Cheap.</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>Thornton</city> 
	 <province>Colorado</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205570760</date> 
 <body>  Um...he's right.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39805215"> 
<user id ="MS_217129174"> 
	 <username>Chris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>95</age> 
	 <city>London</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205570940</date> 
 <body>  He's got a good point. At least he knows a lot more than everyone here...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39811351"> 
<user id ="MS_238935762"> 
	 <username>The Ogre.</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>68</age> 
	 <city>GREEN BAY</city> 
	 <province>Wisconsin</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205581200</date> 
 <body>So basically, he's saying what? That he can't hire people in this country to do with the jobs? Even with the tech visa program? Bullshit. And those support jobs? Guess where they're going? Yup, to India. He may hire tech support people, but they're in a support center in India. Either taht or they are temporary contract workers.  You did realize that he is the reason that companies won't keep a temp worker past a certain time, right? Because gates fired all his hourly non-exempt staff, then hired them back as contract workers? He kept them for years as contract workers. The only difference was that now, he didn' t have to pay benefits or give them the stock options that he had promised them when he hired them as regular workers. The workers sued and won.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39811391"> 
<user id ="MS_238935762"> 
	 <username>The Ogre.</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>68</age> 
	 <city>GREEN BAY</city> 
	 <province>Wisconsin</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205581200</date> 
 <body>  Bullshit. Why can't they hire americans for those jobs?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39811804"> 
<user id ="MS_119052551"> 
	 <username>Carly</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>LAKE WORTH</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205581740</date> 
 <body> Because the majority of engineering majors in america are foreigners. Did you know that?  Most them would like to stay here to work afer their studies, but immigration policies doesn't alllow it...</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39811879"> 
<user id ="MS_128677701"> 
	 <username>Keith</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>VIRGINIA BEACH</city> 
	 <province>Virginia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205581860</date> 
 <body>Bill Gates does not support the american people, only his wallet</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39811940"> 
<user id ="MS_119052551"> 
	 <username>Carly</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>22</age> 
	 <city>LAKE WORTH</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205581920</date> 
 <body>Someone please bring up Lou Dobbs....I can see it coming....</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39811986"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.â„¢</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205581980</date> 
 <body>  Same problem occuring over this side of the pond. 'cept we keep the ones that graduate.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11955_39812183"> 
<user id ="MS_175576456"> 
	 <username>[Queen] Laila.â„¢</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Great city of</city> 
	 <province>London and South East</province> 
	 <country>UK</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1205582220</date> 
 <body>  Ours hasn't progressed that badly. Secondary and College is free, University can be done via a special loan from Gov. So theres no money restricting someone if they want to go Uni. We open our colleges to Europeans and immigrants who are hard working tbh, but then you hear the small amount of British complaining how immigrants are "stealing jobs" (when immigrants do it better)</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>