<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_716_47534155"> 
<user id ="MS_400666827"> 
	 <username>Bryan (Banned again)</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Tampa</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218065820</date> 
 <body>  Too fucking bad.  Discontinued.  Not carried in stores.  Specialty item for a specialty price.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_716_47534300"> 
<user id ="MS_17902449"> 
	 <username>Ronald mcdonald touched my no no spot</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>27</age> 
	 <city>peotone</city> 
	 <province>Illinois</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218066180</date> 
 <body> Well now I guess I must grow my moobs out & grow the coolest porn mustache in the world like yours.Which is fuckin awesome might I add.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_716_47537180"> 
<user id ="MS_166061084"> 
	 <username>Xaphan</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>17</age> 
	 <city>Durango</city> 
	 <province>Colorado</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218074280</date> 
 <body>I like both, but personally like liquor more.  I've actually had a friend constantly down my throat with "No, weed is the way to go!!! You'll feel so much better and less angry!!! Alcohol drinkers are always mad and no fun!!" and it's honestly making me hate the idea of smoking more and more.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_716_47569709"> 
<user id ="MS_385645042"> 
	 <username>mike strobe</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>Lancaster</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218118920</date> 
 <body>    still, you fags dont know that sexual expression beats that shit any time  not that im a perv, its just that,  sexuality is natural. your brain has instincts relating to it. if youre going to do something "bad", do something that nature intends.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_716_47582431"> 
<user id ="MS_22392359"> 
	 <username>[Just Jess]</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>15</age> 
	 <city>Arizona</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218134760</date> 
 <body>weeeeed. always wins.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_716_47584485"> 
<user id ="MS_364446210"> 
	 <username>Zac</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>16</age> 
	 <city>Lancaster</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218137520</date> 
 <body>pot is grown in nature, and saying nature didn't intend for us to smoke pot, is like saying God made a mistake when he created it. agree? same goes for mushrooms and opium. not that ive ever done any of it</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_716_47585770"> 
<user id ="MS_33046351"> 
	 <username>I love how my depression turns to hate so quickly</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>740</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218139320</date> 
 <body>Well weed makes you feel good, and not like puking. Alcohol makes you wanna vomit, and makes u feel that way the next morning.   I think you know which one is win</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_716_47601503"> 
<user id ="MS_72532418"> 
	 <username>â™«Codyâ™«</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>18</age> 
	 <city>bellefontaine.</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218171780</date> 
 <body>Well humm. Ive done my fair share of both in my time. Alchohol, you drink you it, you wait, you get drunk, you keep drinking till you puke and pass out. bam, call it a night. fun night tho right?  Weed, you smoke..you smoke...and if ur a bitch, you pass out real early, cuz you cant handle da dro. BUt sum people. jsut keep smoking and smoking till everything gone and everyones blowed. fun again right?  Then theres both at the same time. which usually leads to blackouts, puking, sex with people you dont know. waking up with no recollection of how you got there. this is fun to, more for memories than action.  My answer to the question tho. Weed, straight up. wanna burn one?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_716_47611726"> 
<user id ="MS_83810061"> 
	 <username>chris</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>CLARKSVILLE</city> 
	 <province>TENNESSEE</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218186300</date> 
 <body>both. 3 shots and a joint will have me set. Though if i had to choose one, then weed by a mile.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_716_47695116"> 
<user id ="MS_158227470"> 
	 <username>Classic Tae Skinny</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>104</age> 
	 <city>CINCINNATI</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218314880</date> 
 <body></body> 
 </post> 
</posts>