<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47704461"> 
<user id ="MS_395242946"> 
	 <username>JAMES</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>60</age> 
	 <city>PITTSBURGH</city> 
	 <province>Pennsylvania</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218338340</date> 
 <body>  Have you ever been in a CEO's office? Or a VP's office?  Why not visit one soon?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47709420"> 
<user id ="MS_369060867"> 
	 <username>Frequency 13</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>104</age> 
	 <city>ATLANTA</city> 
	 <province>Georgia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218350640</date> 
 <body> when the information is on a shared drive or within grasp of their computer for them to get? well ever executive i have known has done so. when it is down the hall being typed by his secretary on a royal typewriter, than no, they do usually send for it...or they send an *gasp* and email asking if someone could email them back the document·which in mccains case he would have to get his wife to come in and help him with</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47717308"> 
<user id ="MS_395242946"> 
	 <username>JAMES</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>60</age> 
	 <city>PITTSBURGH</city> 
	 <province>Pennsylvania</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218364020</date> 
 <body>  Wow. A blast from the past. I remember typewriters.  For skool I had a Smith-Corona and then an Olympia portable, plus one of the first Selectrics, ensconced in student publications offices.  The skool paper set its type every night on Justowriters, which were almost as noisy as pavement breakers.  In my first job I had a Remington manual, then an Olympia manual with more enameled sheet steel than a small fridge.  In the next job, everyone had IBM Selectrics.  Then down the chain to an IBM Executive, with type bars.  The next shop had correcting Selectrics, until the owner bought me a DECmate for Christmas.  Then secretaries became an endangered species.  And middle-aged, highly placed people had to learn how to type.  My heart bled for them.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47729893"> 
<user id ="MS_136643930"> 
	 <username>Josh</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Miami</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218380160</date> 
 <body>  Where I work I get a ton of old people that wont use the "Self Check" at the damn Grocery because they think its stupid and to hard to learn. When all you do is press a button and the machine tells you what to do next.  An executive of a large Copration wouldnt have their job if they didnt know how to use a computer unless they own a lot of stock in the company.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47730427"> 
<user id ="MS_378678777"> 
	 <username>2000man</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>52</age> 
	 <city>Tucker</city> 
	 <province>Georgia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218380880</date> 
 <body>  I'll give you crazy talk. That you would even consider a candidate that the Bilderbergs put in your face all day long day & night. You have to know that is the enemie's favorite. Don't you???</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47730435"> 
<user id ="MS_385379064"> 
	 <username>El King of this Silly Avatar</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Garfield Hts.</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218380880</date> 
 <body>I hope he gets a Myspace account so I can call him a fag.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47737727"> 
<user id ="MS_369060867"> 
	 <username>Frequency 13</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>104</age> 
	 <city>ATLANTA</city> 
	 <province>Georgia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218390780</date> 
 <body> the Bilderbergs LOL you know that list on wikipedia isn't correct. that isn't really where we hold our meetings.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47737961"> 
<user id ="MS_147276825"> 
	 <username>Justin</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>15</age> 
	 <city>Afton</city> 
	 <province>Wyoming</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218391080</date> 
 <body>Ok here is the summary: Obama is the beginning of the end. McCain will just do as Bush is. Either way we are screwed. I mean Obama said he will visit all 57 states. (Muslim States) And McCain is senile and will probably die in a year.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47750011"> 
<user id ="MS_395538055"> 
	 <username>Norseman</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>MINNEAPOLIS</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218409440</date> 
 <body> It says that you are a 104 year old female, What I mean is I graduated in the early 80s and it was a short time after that, PCs were introduced into my school most people my age either learned about computers because of there job or they learned because they wanted to on there own. For me it was a little of both. I cant imagine why a person wouldnt want to learn how to use a PC in this day and age but apparently Mccain chose not to.Mccain has been a senator for many years and his lack of computer skills has not hampered his elections to this point and I dont think it will hamper his presidentual bid. The issues are more important than whether he know how to operate a PC. But I do understand what you are saying.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47751219"> 
<user id ="MS_395538055"> 
	 <username>Norseman</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>MINNEAPOLIS</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218411900</date> 
 <body> Maybe they refuse to use it, I wont use it simply because if there is a live human that probably needs a job one Isle down, I will go to them. If corporations had there way there wouldnt be anyone at the checkouts. So every time you use the self checkout you are sending a message arnt you.Do you get a discount on your goods when you use the self checkout?</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>