<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47730427"> 
<user id ="MS_378678777"> 
	 <username>2000man</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>52</age> 
	 <city>Tucker</city> 
	 <province>Georgia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218380880</date> 
 <body>  I'll give you crazy talk. That you would even consider a candidate that the Bilderbergs put in your face all day long day & night. You have to know that is the enemie's favorite. Don't you???</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47730435"> 
<user id ="MS_385379064"> 
	 <username>El King of this Silly Avatar</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Garfield Hts.</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218380880</date> 
 <body>I hope he gets a Myspace account so I can call him a fag.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47737727"> 
<user id ="MS_369060867"> 
	 <username>Frequency 13</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>104</age> 
	 <city>ATLANTA</city> 
	 <province>Georgia</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218390780</date> 
 <body> the Bilderbergs LOL you know that list on wikipedia isn't correct. that isn't really where we hold our meetings.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47737961"> 
<user id ="MS_147276825"> 
	 <username>Justin</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>15</age> 
	 <city>Afton</city> 
	 <province>Wyoming</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218391080</date> 
 <body>Ok here is the summary: Obama is the beginning of the end. McCain will just do as Bush is. Either way we are screwed. I mean Obama said he will visit all 57 states. (Muslim States) And McCain is senile and will probably die in a year.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47750011"> 
<user id ="MS_395538055"> 
	 <username>Norseman</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>MINNEAPOLIS</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218409440</date> 
 <body> It says that you are a 104 year old female, What I mean is I graduated in the early 80s and it was a short time after that, PCs were introduced into my school most people my age either learned about computers because of there job or they learned because they wanted to on there own. For me it was a little of both. I cant imagine why a person wouldnt want to learn how to use a PC in this day and age but apparently Mccain chose not to.Mccain has been a senator for many years and his lack of computer skills has not hampered his elections to this point and I dont think it will hamper his presidentual bid. The issues are more important than whether he know how to operate a PC. But I do understand what you are saying.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47751219"> 
<user id ="MS_395538055"> 
	 <username>Norseman</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>MINNEAPOLIS</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218411900</date> 
 <body> Maybe they refuse to use it, I wont use it simply because if there is a live human that probably needs a job one Isle down, I will go to them. If corporations had there way there wouldnt be anyone at the checkouts. So every time you use the self checkout you are sending a message arnt you.Do you get a discount on your goods when you use the self checkout?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47751322"> 
<user id ="MS_395538055"> 
	 <username>Norseman</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>MINNEAPOLIS</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218412080</date> 
 <body> I would say OBAMMMA</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47751926"> 
<user id ="MS_171407912"> 
	 <username>Binky</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>20</age> 
	 <city>Temple Terrace</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218413520</date> 
 <body>hmmm....a president who isnt going to be using google or wikipedia in office, what a shame  computer skills may be a necessary skill in many other important jobs, but i dont really see it being essential for the president</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47752227"> 
<user id ="MS_395538055"> 
	 <username>Norseman</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>MINNEAPOLIS</city> 
	 <province>Minnesota</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218414300</date> 
 <body>Its not... they want to attack Mccaine any way they can, but I do wonder why he never learned just for fun, I love my PC unless it crashes for no reason whatsoever!</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10335_47752310"> 
<user id ="MS_195642716"> 
	 <username>Æon</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>26</age> 
	 <city>ΓΦΔΞΘΘξς</city> 
	 <province>Omniverse</province> 
	 <country>VA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1218414480</date> 
 <body>  Ya know, all things considered, being the president of the US ain't no big deal.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>