<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_9902_49794289"> 
<user id ="MS_285803594"> 
	 <username>Meg.</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Concord</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221750840</date> 
 <body></body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9902_49794839"> 
<user id ="MS_1766140"> 
	 <username>Corey</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>23</age> 
	 <city>MESQUITE</city> 
	 <province>TEXAS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221751620</date> 
 <body>social heathcare will fail in this country it hasnt worked anywhere else it wont work here.  i belive we need to make healthcare a little cheaper to a certain degree. we shouldnt just give it away like to do food stamps. the more u give stuff away like that the higher prices go up so you still cant get it. its like when he said if u just tax the corps. they just go up on prices what we need to do is not tax anyone more but to stop all the loop holes in the system. you can raise the tax all you want on the rich they will just find a way out of it.  oh and on you stupid comment about 250K being rich yeah like 30 years ago. my Father makes 140k alone that doesnt include all th bonouses he gets through out the year and the investments he has made and yet he is still struggling a little not alot but he odesnt have a maid or personal driver in fact he dives a 1997 dondge intrepid that needs new brakes and belts. yes he does things with my mom time to time but they work thier ass off to save money for trips. we went from being in a trailer trach area to living in a nicer town. its not 90210 but its safer and better then what we had before and its cuz he worked his ass off and still does.  Sure thier are those who do work hard that need help but thier are just as many in the lower class that dont do anything that expect the govermnt to take care of them and its bull. go watch and see people get food stamps and watch the poeple who pull up in escallades with 22's go get some. its bull so whats going to happen is now my dad and mom are going to have to pay more taxes of rthem to get more free stuff from the gov.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9902_49825281"> 
<user id ="MS_285803594"> 
	 <username>Meg.</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Concord</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221809100</date> 
 <body>140k is not 250k  it is 110k less.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9902_49850954"> 
<user id ="MS_143745876"> 
	 <username>Not THE Vault Dweller, but a Vault dweller.</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Nawlins</city> 
	 <province>Louisiana</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221846000</date> 
 <body>My uncles make about 250k a year, and the only expensive car they own, is a VW Golf. No butlers, hookers, personal servants, maids, yaddayaddayadda. 28,ooo and barely surviving? Pfft. That's a fine income, now add your husbands into that. Now, if that is both of your incomes combined, you are still well off, just don't have any kids anytime soon. Maybe 28,000 isn't that much in your area? No animal testing products are everywhere, even at your local wally world.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9902_49851136"> 
<user id ="MS_143745876"> 
	 <username>Not THE Vault Dweller, but a Vault dweller.</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>19</age> 
	 <city>Nawlins</city> 
	 <province>Louisiana</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221846300</date> 
 <body> We're not all lazy and jobless, we're just fucking poor.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9902_49853456"> 
<user id ="MS_100055634"> 
	 <username>Michigan Mike</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>30</age> 
	 <city>ANN ARBOR</city> 
	 <province>Michigan</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221850020</date> 
 <body>  Trillionaires? Name one. Just one.  And that was the most brilliant thing said in the entire post.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9902_49869093"> 
<user id ="MS_378229142"> 
	 <username>Ed O</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>49</age> 
	 <city>REDMOND</city> 
	 <province>Oregon</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221888060</date> 
 <body>  Hi Meg. Yesterady [sic] you said "...really because me & my husband have a trust with morgan stanley and we just lost about a HUNDRED thousand dollars today."  http://forums.myspace.com/t/4177476.aspx?fuseaction=forums.viewt hread  What I find amazing is that you and your husband have over 100k sitting in a trust, and your Mom is living in a 500sf ghetto. Mom must be so proud of the daughter she raised; to be so wealthy and not help your own Mom.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9902_49872070"> 
<user id ="MS_377264914"> 
	 <username>Dr John Zoidberg</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>57</age> 
	 <city>Two Rivers</city> 
	 <province>Iowa</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221894360</date> 
 <body>     How dare you have a memory, ED.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9902_49994320"> 
<user id ="MS_246598765"> 
	 <username>**Spoil'n*My*Girls**</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>99</age> 
	 <city>California</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222109760</date> 
 <body>   Your mother is in a ghettos (in or around Concord no less) - and yet you are eating organic food at a premium price? Doesn't it occur to you that paying it back to your mom might be in order? I am fascinated by your arguments and yet it doesn't add up. How much research have you done? Have you reviewed the reality that free healthcare results in substantial lines for people in need of quick response? Have you researched the quality of care that is offered by such programs? Have you (at 19 yrs of age) really PAID taxes to the extent that you understand when the rates go up or down based on income?  As for your husbands parents paying $1700 a month....well that is just plain STUPIDITY. Most healthcare offered to the working class through an employer nets about $300 - $500 a month for a family plan. Given that, I think your inlaws need to do some research cuz they are getting screwed......  You might want to show them the following (from a quick Google) which shows the HealthCare Matrix for CA. http://www.coverageforall.org/pdf/matrix/CA_Matrix.pdf  Given this.....I cannot understand your argument - It doesn't add up at all....and for the record, I am not even a 'right winger' as you put it.....which should tell you something......</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_9902_50001145"> 
<user id ="MS_11188085"> 
	 <username>Devin a des rêves</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>Pueblo</city> 
	 <province>Colorado</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222122900</date> 
 <body>   </body> 
 </post> 
</posts>