<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49739915"> 
<user id ="MS_289754314"> 
	 <username>Nate the Great 08</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Fairport</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221664500</date> 
 <body>So what's really going on? Did the democratic nomination slip their grasp with Clinton or do they secretly have their strings attached to Obama, the same as they did and still do for McCain? If you recall, I covered this a few weeks ago. This Bilderberg swinger family was hosting fund raisers and and making public pleas, pushing for the nominations of Hillary Clinton AND John McCain. See that story at the bottom, below the following update.   Hillary Clinton’s rich friend Lady de Rothschild ambushes Barack Obama Diehard Hillary fans plan to protest at the party’s crowning of Obama – and may even vote for John McCain   Lynn Forrester De Rothschild   Times Online August 17, 2008 Sarah Baxter  At the Democratic national convention next week, Lynn Forester, Lady de Rothschild, one of Britain’s most influential political hostesses, will be contemplating treachery. She poured her heart and money into Hillary Clinton’s campaign and she is thinking of voting for John McCain, the Republican candidate, for president.   She is not impressed by Barack Obama and doubts he will reach the White House. “My loyalty is to the Democrats winning. Barack Obama is going to have a serious problem getting elected, for good reason,” she said in an interview.   “The party needs to face the fact that without Hillary Clinton on the ticket, the Democrats will probably lose. ”  Rothschild, 54, is a New York businesswoman and top fundraiser for Clinton who married into the British banking dynasty.   The billionaire Sir Evelyn de Rothschild, 22 years her senior and former chairman of the family firm, NM Rothschild, will be with her in Denver when Obama is crowned the victor. She regards the presumptive Democratic nominee, 47, as something of a usurper.   The Rothschilds spent the night of their wedding dinner in the Lincoln bedroom at the White House when Bill Clinton was president, so her loyalty to Hillary is understandable. However, the passionate distrust of Obama shared by many Clinton supporters is turning into a headache for the Democrats.   Leon Panetta, Bill Clinton’s former White House chief of staff, was tasked by the Obama campaign this summer with soothing ruffled feelings and helping Hillary loyalists to get over their sense of loss. It has been a demanding assignment.   “There is a sense of entitlement that almost seems to be inbred,” Panetta said. “They are convinced Hillary is the one who should be assuming the mantle and it’s tough to crack that. ”  Rothschild is the founder of Together4Us, a group formed to “honour” Clinton and the nearly 18m voters who supported her in the primaries. Among its demands were a state-by-state roll-call of votes - a final show of muscle by the vanquished Clinton - and a prime speaking slot for her.    FULL ARTICLE     Rothschild Banking Dynasty Pushing Both Clinton & McCain???  It's long been alleged in the conspiracy underground that a hierarchy of Jewish banking interests intend to unify the planet under the banner of a fascist world state, all under their control but my suspicions about the Rothschild family in the article herein, needn't extend past the family itself. After all, their alleged - Because I cannot say how accurate the alllegations are - past methods of operation in the banking and political arenas are for all I know, one of, if not the predominate reason for the most recent suspicions that are cast broadly and often unfairly, over the entire Jewish community or merely it's more visible movers and shakers who may not only be unassociated with the Rothschild family but vehemently opposed to it.   I'm certainly late to the game in noticing what I am about to showcase but perhaps no later than anybody else in the world of multimedia, as a brief Google search retrieves no such discussion of what is perhaps, one of the Rothschild family's latest power moves in the world of mergers and acquisitions.   It turns out that Lynn Forrester de Rothschild, wife of Sir Evelyn de Rothschild, had at least until recent months, been publicly supporting Hillary Clinton on television (see 1st youtube clip at bottom) and in print media interviews. Lynn's husband Evelyn de Rothschild was the head of the English arm of his family's banking dynasty until the recent purchase of his stake by Paris-Orleans, the French arm of the Rothschild dynasty, though the century old split was united with an operational merger just four years ago.   Well it also turns out that John McCain is also being pushed by members of the Rothschild family. Evelyn de Rothschild's cousin Jacob's son, Nathaniel Philip de Rothschild, is pushing for a John McCain presidency. He and his father held a campaign fundraiser for McCain in London earlier this year.   So I have to wonder.. is there really a political split on the British side of the Rothschild banking family? Were Nathaniel de Rothschild's father Jacob and his cousin Evelyn really vying for McCain and Clinton respectively and at the expense of each other or do both sides support, well, both sides? That is to suggest the cousins wanted McCain and Clinton to clinch their respective nominations because all rhetoric aside, each intends to carry out their duties the same as the other or perhaps more realistically, the pools of influence that each is a spokesmen for, intend to manage things the same or will have no choice in the matter if constraining conditions - brought to bear by people like the Rothschilds with their public and private political and financial influence - are a factor.   And it does appear they are a factor, as Lynn Forrestor de Rothschild met husband Evelyn at the 1998 Bilderberg conference. They were introduced by legendary 'public servant' Henry Kissinger, who himself has wielded incredible political and private financial influence for decades, as a great deal of Bilderberg attendees do.   But what is to be said of Barack Obama? Is he outside the influence of the Rothschild family or their affiliates? My guess is no and that one of the most renown and influential multi-generational families on the planet are not going to lose the 2008 election.           Lynn Forrester de Rothschild          Nathaniel Philip de Rothschild</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49740231"> 
<user id ="MS_289754314"> 
	 <username>Nate the Great 08</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Fairport</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221664980</date> 
 <body>So why is Lady DeRotshchild so concered about the dems losing the election if her nephew Philip is pushing McCain? Is there a split between her husband Evelyn Rothschild and his brother Jacob, whose son hosted a fundraiser for John McCain?</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49740879"> 
<user id ="MS_475921"> 
	 <username>JASON HUN</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>100</age> 
	 <city>L.A. - Orange County area</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221665880</date> 
 <body>if u have billions of dollars, u buy both candidates --what's a couple million when u have billions (thousands of millions)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49741480"> 
<user id ="MS_289754314"> 
	 <username>Nate the Great 08</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Fairport</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221666720</date> 
 <body>  the Rothschild family has allegedly been highly involved on both ends of the political spectrum for hundreds of years and have even allegedly been involved in coercion of markets through media and black-ops along with JP Morgan interests and the Rockefellers.  Those are three families that the fringe conspiracy research community have addressed for decades. It's just strange how Bearn Stearns collapses and is eaten up by JP Morgan Chase (formerly run by David Rockefeller) last fall and now the Rothschilds are very publicly pushing the one party system, masquerading as two.  The 'conspiracy theorists' are gaining more validity by the day.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49742836"> 
<user id ="MS_12550638"> 
	 <username>pete</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>56</age> 
	 <city>ontario</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221668580</date> 
 <body>She must have huge balls, and should be pushing a wheel barrow to accuse Obama of being an elitest ,, I sat back and laughed that she dare say this with a straight face. Who's kidding who, she would change parties to support the candidate that can be influenced to support an attack on Iran,, that must mean she thinks McCain will do it while Obama will use diplomacy.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49744009"> 
<user id ="MS_289754314"> 
	 <username>Nate the Great 08</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Fairport</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221670020</date> 
 <body>the Rothschilds literally bank the intellectual laziness of the American people.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49744976"> 
<user id ="MS_12550638"> 
	 <username>pete</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>56</age> 
	 <city>ontario</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221671100</date> 
 <body>She is helping the Obama campaign by making such nonsensical comments and will people will look at her as they do McCain , he doesnt know how many houses he owns, with a wife worth a fortune, how she understand what the middle class is suffering and call Obama an "elitest".</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49745012"> 
<user id ="MS_61142930"> 
	 <username>Just to post sh*t</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>CHICAGO</city> 
	 <province>ILLINOIS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221671160</date> 
 <body> What difference does it make? U conspiracy theorist believe everyone in government is part of NWO. McCain, Obama, or Clinton what's the point of this. Its all the same conclusion. World domination.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49745531"> 
<user id ="MS_289754314"> 
	 <username>Nate the Great 08</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Fairport</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221671760</date> 
 <body>No Eddie, I don't believe they're in control of every candidate. They're an interlocking group at Bilderberg. It's not all one big conspiracy. There are circles of influence and infighting, I'm sure.  It's not difficult at all to trace the Clintons, Bushes, McCains, Bidens and Obamas of the world to mega powerful corporations whose vice-presidents and board members meet with agents of the two parties at various forums and conferences, Bilderberg being one of them. It's a revolving door of private finance and corporate and state alliances that border on fascism. When each candidate is only a degree or two removed from each other through influence peddlers who've traveled back and forth between the political and financial world and can be documented as to making a killing off the post-9/11 thiefdom economy, you've got a problem.  It's not so easily though, to connect Ron Paul (republican), Ralph Nader (independent), Cynthia McKinney (green) and Bob Barr (libertarian) to the same network of Iraq war marketers and opportunists.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49749008"> 
<user id ="MS_408309640"> 
	 <username>Cters are confusing</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>99</age> 
	 <city>Burney</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221676020</date> 
 <body> well nate think of it this way. The european banking cartels have been finacing both sides of every war for 200+ years. there is where you should look.  or here. Kinds of a funny about the fed.   http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/26754130</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>