<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49740879"> 
<user id ="MS_475921"> 
	 <username>JASON HUN</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>100</age> 
	 <city>L.A. - Orange County area</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221665880</date> 
 <body>if u have billions of dollars, u buy both candidates --what's a couple million when u have billions (thousands of millions)</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49741480"> 
<user id ="MS_289754314"> 
	 <username>Nate the Great 08</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Fairport</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221666720</date> 
 <body>  the Rothschild family has allegedly been highly involved on both ends of the political spectrum for hundreds of years and have even allegedly been involved in coercion of markets through media and black-ops along with JP Morgan interests and the Rockefellers.  Those are three families that the fringe conspiracy research community have addressed for decades. It's just strange how Bearn Stearns collapses and is eaten up by JP Morgan Chase (formerly run by David Rockefeller) last fall and now the Rothschilds are very publicly pushing the one party system, masquerading as two.  The 'conspiracy theorists' are gaining more validity by the day.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49742836"> 
<user id ="MS_12550638"> 
	 <username>pete</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>56</age> 
	 <city>ontario</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221668580</date> 
 <body>She must have huge balls, and should be pushing a wheel barrow to accuse Obama of being an elitest ,, I sat back and laughed that she dare say this with a straight face. Who's kidding who, she would change parties to support the candidate that can be influenced to support an attack on Iran,, that must mean she thinks McCain will do it while Obama will use diplomacy.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49744009"> 
<user id ="MS_289754314"> 
	 <username>Nate the Great 08</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Fairport</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221670020</date> 
 <body>the Rothschilds literally bank the intellectual laziness of the American people.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49744976"> 
<user id ="MS_12550638"> 
	 <username>pete</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>56</age> 
	 <city>ontario</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>CA</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221671100</date> 
 <body>She is helping the Obama campaign by making such nonsensical comments and will people will look at her as they do McCain , he doesnt know how many houses he owns, with a wife worth a fortune, how she understand what the middle class is suffering and call Obama an "elitest".</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49745012"> 
<user id ="MS_61142930"> 
	 <username>Just to post sh*t</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>CHICAGO</city> 
	 <province>ILLINOIS</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221671160</date> 
 <body> What difference does it make? U conspiracy theorist believe everyone in government is part of NWO. McCain, Obama, or Clinton what's the point of this. Its all the same conclusion. World domination.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49745531"> 
<user id ="MS_289754314"> 
	 <username>Nate the Great 08</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>29</age> 
	 <city>Fairport</city> 
	 <province>Ohio</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221671760</date> 
 <body>No Eddie, I don't believe they're in control of every candidate. They're an interlocking group at Bilderberg. It's not all one big conspiracy. There are circles of influence and infighting, I'm sure.  It's not difficult at all to trace the Clintons, Bushes, McCains, Bidens and Obamas of the world to mega powerful corporations whose vice-presidents and board members meet with agents of the two parties at various forums and conferences, Bilderberg being one of them. It's a revolving door of private finance and corporate and state alliances that border on fascism. When each candidate is only a degree or two removed from each other through influence peddlers who've traveled back and forth between the political and financial world and can be documented as to making a killing off the post-9/11 thiefdom economy, you've got a problem.  It's not so easily though, to connect Ron Paul (republican), Ralph Nader (independent), Cynthia McKinney (green) and Bob Barr (libertarian) to the same network of Iraq war marketers and opportunists.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49749008"> 
<user id ="MS_408309640"> 
	 <username>Cters are confusing</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>99</age> 
	 <city>Burney</city> 
	 <province>California</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221676020</date> 
 <body> well nate think of it this way. The european banking cartels have been finacing both sides of every war for 200+ years. there is where you should look.  or here. Kinds of a funny about the fed.   http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/26754130</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49766087"> 
<user id ="MS_387837884"> 
	 <username>Oldman</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>24</age> 
	 <city>US</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country></country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221712380</date> 
 <body> The House of Rothschild was worth billions well over a century ago.  Today they are likely to be worth hundreds of trillions of dollars.    This book by Dr. John Coleman, author of The Committee of 300, tells how Mayer Amschel, the founder of the “Red Shield” dynasty, acquired his first fortune. It is a far cry from the myths and legends that still surround the man who began as a rag and bone merchant and pawnbroker, working out of a small house on Judenstrasse, Frankfurt on the Main, Germany, where he lived with his wife and family. The events attributed to history are often caused by a “hidden hand” pulling the strings of kings, emperors, princes and potentates from behind the scenes. This phenomenon is explained, and the legends that have grown up around the Rothschilds are demolished by this book that also reveals the Rothschild’s intriguing that brought down men like Napoleon and Tsar Alexander II of Russia. Legend has it that Mayer Amschel Rothschild’s “genius and financial skills” were inherited by his sons, but the truth is quite a different story, as Dr. Coleman makes very clear in this well documented account that goes far beyond the best known legends cloaking the true character of the family. Exactly how Mayer Amschel Rothschild “struck it lucky” and the steps he took that brought the family from obscurity to “virtual rulers of all Europe,” makes fascinating reading. This outstanding book is not only about the past, it is also about the present and the future. It will help to explain many of the events that perplex the ordinary people like the war in Iraq and the war threats against Iran.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_11661_49771505"> 
<user id ="MS_35280508"> 
	 <username>LuCidiTy</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>Alpha Centauri</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UM</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1221721920</date> 
 <body>i choked when she called obama elitist.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>