<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
 <posts> 
<post id= "MS_10353_49982425"> 
<user id ="MS_386574613"> 
	 <username>Dr</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>36</age> 
	 <city>Miami Beach</city> 
	 <province>Florida</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222091820</date> 
 <body>Daily Article byFrank Shostak|Posted on 9/22/2008  Given last week's dramatic events — the bankruptcy of LehmanBrothers, the end of Merrill Lynch's independence, and an $85 billionUS-government bailout of insurer AIG — most financial institutions arelikely to become more sensitive to the state of their net worth. For instance, all it takes for a financial institution that has anet worth of $30 billion and assets of $600 billion to go under is forthe value of assets to fall by 5%. In the current financial climate, itcan easily happen; hence, most financial institutions are not immunefrom the potential threat of going belly up. One of the major reasons why the Fed rescued AIG was to prevent afall in the value of bank assets, a fall that would in turn exposetheir true net worth and cause (it is generally believed) a run onbanks that would decimate the entire banking system. As long as the AIGcan keep paying the banks' losses for their suspect (but insured)investments, those banks don't need to reappraise their true values. But there is always the lingering fear that at some stage banks willbe forced to disclose market-related valuations and that this could setin motion a financial tsunami. Mortgage-linked assets are regarded as being at the root of thepresent credit crisis — the worst since the Great Depression. Toeliminate a potential threat from devalued mortgage-linked assets, USTreasury Secretary Paulson and Fed Chairman Bernanke are planning tomove these assets from the balance sheets of financial companies into anew institution. The Bush administration is asking Congress to let thegovernment buy $700 billion in bad mortgages as part of the largestfinancial bailout since the Great Depression. The plan would give the government broad power to buy the bad debtof any US financial institutions for the next two years. It would alsoraise the statutory limit on the national debt from $10.6 trillion to$11.3 trillion. But how is the transfer of bad paper assets to some new institutionand their replacement with a better quality of assets — withTreasuries, let us say — going to fix the economy? How can it reversethe present slump in the housing market? The Treasury and the Fed believe that allowing financialinstitutions to get rid of bad assets will remove the threat of banks'having to assign correct values to their suspect assets. It is heldthis will bring things back to normal, that the banks will startexpanding mortgage loans and revive the housing market and in turn theeconomy. But allowing banks to get rid of bad assets doesn't imply that theywill be keen to expand mortgage lending, thereby accumulating newpotentially bad assets. At present, for most US banks, the major concern is improving theirnet worth, i.e., strengthening their solvency. This means that banksare likely to slow the pace of expansion of their assets, and thevolume of lending is likely to come under pressure. In the week endingSeptember 10, commercial banks' total assets fell by $33.9 billion. Theyearly rate of growth of total assets fell to 4.9% from 6.7% in Augustand 12.7% in March. According to the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC),commercial banks and savings institutions' net worth fell by $10billion from Q1 to Q2. This was the first decline since the data wasmade available in Q2 2000. At the root of the problem are not mortgage-backed assets as suchbut the Fed's boom-bust policies. It is the extremely loose monetarypolicy between January 2001 and June 2004 that set in motion themassive housing bubble (the federal-funds-rate target was lowered from6% to 1%). It is the tighter stance between June 2004 and September2007 that burst the housing bubble (the federal-funds-rate target waslifted from 1% to 5.25%). The tighter monetary stance put a brake on the diversion of realsavings toward bubble activities. Now the effect of a change inmonetary policy operates with a time lag. We suggest that the tighterinterest stance of the Fed between June 2004 and September 2007 has sofar only hit the real-estate market and financial institutions. Various bubble activities that sprang up on the back of loosemonetary policy between January 2001 and June 2004 are not only in thereal-estate and financial sectors; they are also in the other parts ofthe economy. Consequently, there is a growing likelihood that these activitieswill come under pressure. Since they are the product of loose monetarypolicy, obviously the banks that supported them are going to incur morebad assets, which will put more pressure on banks' net worth. The US Congress May Help Bernanke to Increase Monetary Expansion The rescue package is a combined act by the US Treasury and the Fedand is seen by experts as a comprehensive approach since it alsoaddresses the issue of liquidity. The chairman of the Fed, who isfearful that the American economy could plunge into depression, holdsthat the only way to prevent this is through massive monetary pumping. We suspect that Bernanke is of the view that he hasn't been allowedto operate "properly" to prevent the current upheavals in financialmarkets because he wasn't free to pump money at liberty. In the present setup of interest targeting, the Fed cannot simplypump money unhindered into the economy and boost monetary liquidity.Monetary pumping, while the federal-funds rate is at its target, willpush the rate below the target. To bring the federal-funds rate back tothe target the Fed is obliged to sell assets such as Treasuries toabsorb money from the federal-funds market. All this means that if there is no upward pressure on thefederal-funds rate, the Fed cannot pump money without pushing the ratebelow the target. For instance, if the Fed increases lending to afinancial institution, the new money that will enter the financialmarket will put downward pressure on the federal-funds rate. To eliminate this downward pressure, the Fed will be obliged to sellTreasury securities. By selling these securities, the Fed takes moneyfrom the market. In this way the US central bank offsets the downwardpressure on the federal-funds rate brought about by the increase inlending to financial institutions. Note that the holdings of Treasuriesby the Fed play an important role in the process that we have described. As a result of all the actions to boost liquidity taken by the Fedsince August 10, 2007, the US central bank holdings of US Treasurysecurities has dwindled. Just a year ago, the Fed held $780 billion inTreasuries; by September 17, 2008, this has fallen to $480 billion.Year-on-year Treasury securities holdings by the Fed fell by 38.8% inAugust after falling by 39.4% the month before. This was the tenthconsecutive month of yearly decline. So far in September, the yearly rate of growth has stood at negative38.5%. If we allow for the $200 billion that the Fed pledged to theTerm Securities Lending Facility and the $85 billion loan to AIG thenthe amount falls to $195 billion. If more institutions are on the brink of bankruptcy, and the Feddecides to provide support to them, it would have difficulty in doingso without a sufficient inventory of Treasuries. Again, if the Fed wereto run out of Treasuries, then any lending by the Fed would lead thefederal-funds rate to fall below the target. To help out the Fed, last Wednesday, the US Treasury announced thatit would auction $100 billion in debt in order to offset the monetarypumping by the Fed. Observe again that the Fed has officially been engaged in actions toboost liquidity since August 10, 2007. All this means that the Fedmight appear to be loose, but in reality, the overall pumping by theFed, as depicted by its balance sheet so far, has been moderate. The yearly rate of growth of the Fed's assets stood at 4% in Augustagainst 3.8% in July. Note that since November 2004, the growthmomentum of the Fed's assets has been in a downtrend (the yearly rateof growth in November 2004 stood at 7.1%). How Can the Fed Boost the Money Supply? So how can the Fed boost the money supply without pushing thefederal-funds rate to below the target? One way of achieving this is byasking the Treasury to issue more debt. Once the Treasury sells moredebt to the public, this absorbs money from the federal-funds market.As a result the federal-funds rate will be pushed above the target.Once this happens, the Fed will step in by buying the Treasuries fromthe public. Remember that, by buying Treasuries the Fed injects money into thefederal-funds market. The new money in turn pushes the federal-fundsrate back towards the target. The final outcome of all this is that themoney supply has increased and the Fed now has more Treasuries, i.e.,its balance sheet has increased. Now this way of boosting money supply and monetary liquidity issomewhat cumbersome. It also raises the level of the Treasury debt andpushes long-term yields and hence mortgage interest rates higher thanthey would have been. The better way, according to Bernanke and US central bank officials,is to pump money any time they think it is necessary. Not only willthis boost monetary liquidity but it will also boost the Treasuriesholdings by the Fed. (Remember: to pump money, the Fed buys Treasuries.) But how can this be done, given the fact that to keep thefederal-funds rate at the target prevents the Fed from pumping money atliberty? A solution is on its way — to pay interest on bank deposits held atthe Fed. By paying banks an interest rate, which corresponds to thetarget rate, the Fed removes from banks the incentive to lend surpluscash to each other. As a result, the federal-funds rate will not fallbelow the target in response to the Fed's monetary pumping. (Remember: when more money is pumped, banks' surplus cash increases.To get rid of the greater surplus, they will agree to lend at a lowerinterest rate than before.) When every bank is guaranteed interest on its deposit with the Fed,banks will not lend to each other — why bother to lend and incur riskif a bank will be paid interest by just keeping the money at the Fed?Consequently, the interest rate will not decline in response to theincrease in the Fed's pumping. With this setup, the Fed could pumpmoney at liberty without pushing the federal-funds rate to below thetarget. We suspect that against the background of last week's events and theemerging view that something drastic must be done to prevent acalamity, there is a high likelihood that the Congress is going toapprove the Fed's (i.e., Bernanke's) request for paying interest tobanks very soon. Once the Congress gives the green light, Bernanke willstart pushing a massive amount of money to soften the crisis in thecredit markets. The idea is that this should boost bank lending, which in turn willkick-start the economy. Some experts are arguing that the Fed needs topump over $1 trillion to make things work. Can More Money Fix the Current Economic Crisis? But why should pumping more money do the trick? It seems that, formost experts, money is an agent for economic growth. Money however isjust a medium of exchange and cannot create real wealth as such. On thecontrary, monetary expansion results in the squandering of real wealthand economic impoverishment (look at Zimbabwe). If the pool of realsavings is declining, then real economic growth will follow suitregardless of how much money the Fed is going to pump. Declining household net worth raises the likelihood that the pool ofreal savings could be in trouble. According to the Federal Reserveflow-of-funds data, the net wealth of households fell 0.8% in Q2 asboth home values and financial-asset values fell. This was the third consecutive quarterly decline. In its pressrelease, the Fed said it has never before recorded three consecutivequarters of declining household wealth since it began trackingquarterly changes in 1951. Year-on-year net wealth fell by 3.5% in Q2after falling by 0.7% in Q1. Conclusions The Bush administration is asking Congress to let the government buy$700 billion in bad mortgages as part of the largest financial bailoutsince the Great Depression. The plan would give the government broadpower to buy the bad debt of any US financial institutions for the nexttwo years. It would also raise the statutory limit on the national debtfrom $10.6 trillion to $11.3 trillion. At the root of the problem are not mortgage-backed assets as suchbut the Fed's boom-bust policies. It is the extremely loose monetarypolicy between January 2001 and June 2004 that set in motion themassive housing bubble (the federal-funds-rate target was lowered from6% to 1%). It is the tighter stance between June 2004 and September2007 that burst the housing bubble (the federal-funds-rate target waslifted from 1% to 5.25%).     Can the "rescue plan" fix the US economy, or will it plunge us into the mother of all recessions? On account of the time lag, we suggest that the tighter intereststance of the Fed between June 2004 and September 2007 has so far onlyhit the real-estate market and financial institutions. Various bubble activities that sprang up on the back of loosemonetary policy between January 2001 and June 2004 are not only in thereal-estate and financial sectors; they are also in the other parts ofthe economy. Consequently, there is a growing likelihood that these activitieswill come under pressure in the month ahead regardless of the rescuepackage. Since these activities are the product of loose monetarypolicy, obviously the banks that supported them are going to incur morebad assets, which will put more pressure on banks' net worth. Contrary to popular belief, the rescue package cannot help theeconomy; it will only severely weaken wealth generators. (The largerthe package, the more misery it will inflict.) Hence, once the massiverescue plan is implemented, it will not prevent an economic slump but,rather, runs the risk of plunging the economy into the mother of allrecessions.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10353_50011028"> 
<user id ="MS_411320050"> 
	 <username>Tarconis</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>42</age> 
	 <city>LEXINGTON</city> 
	 <province>Kentucky</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222151460</date> 
 <body>My concern, (as far as I have read, and understand it) is that if the government goes ahead with the bailout, is that so far there's been no discussion about Implimenting any regulator practices in the bail out.  So we give Wall street this money, what assurances do we get that wall street won't continue the practices, and policies that got them in trouble in the first place?  Secondly, the plan so far (as far as I have learned) is that the government is going to buy all this bad debt from Wall street, Using the newly acquired Fannie May & Freddie Mac, to buy these debts, (these debts are from bad mortgage loans, that Fannie May & Freddie Mac needed rescue from) so now we're going to let this giant government corporation aquire a massive debt (that it couldn't pay for in the first place) with money that it either doesn't, or didn't have, to cover bad investments that may not ever be able to become profitable, and could be sold at a loss (to companies That don't have the money to buy them anyway) and in the end Fannie May & Freddie Mac ends up Bankrupt again, ONLY this time it's not only Wall Street that's in the throws of bankruptcy..... It's the entire nation, along with all her citizens.  So I personaly don't see any silver lining to this noxious cloud hanging over this nations head.  All I see is this is a measure that will only slow down what may well be an eventual second depression.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10353_50015856"> 
<user id ="MS_35280508"> 
	 <username>LuCidiTy</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>Alpha Centauri</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UM</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222158480</date> 
 <body>no.  this is only the beginning.  and this is a financial crisis on a global scale.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10353_50016018"> 
<user id ="MS_35280508"> 
	 <username>LuCidiTy</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>46</age> 
	 <city>Alpha Centauri</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>UM</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222158660</date> 
 <body>in other words, even these band-aids will only hold us together temporarily...there is WAY more to come. corporations who have been stealing and cheating and throwing our jobs away for the quick buck. there is nowhere for us to GO in the global market...we don't SELL or MAKE anything anymore and we BOUGHT everything on credit and now it's all vapor. china's gonna miss our consumer dollars and they'll come to a virtual standstill but they'll be okay in the end just not on as large a scale.</body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10353_50016195"> 
<user id ="MS_399467372"> 
	 <username>JM</username> 
	 <sex>M</sex> 
	 <age>33</age> 
	 <city>Wisconsin</city> 
	 <province></province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222158900</date> 
 <body>"If the American people ever allow private banks to control the issuance of their currency, first by inflation and then by deflation, the banks and corporations that will grow up around them will deprive the people of all their property until their children will wake up homeless on the continent their fathers conquered. The issuing power of money should be taken from banks and restored to Congress and the people to whom it belongs. I sincerely believe the banking institutions having the issuing power of money, are more dangerous to liberty than standing armies."  -Thomas Jefferson, Letter to James Monroe, January 1, 1815  </body> 
 </post> 
<post id= "MS_10353_50016550"> 
<user id ="MS_399483676"> 
	 <username>deb</username> 
	 <sex>F</sex> 
	 <age>56</age> 
	 <city>CHARLOTTE</city> 
	 <province>North Carolina</province> 
	 <country>US</country> 
	 </user> 
<date>1222159320</date> 
 <body>It might work if some of the money goes to main street, and doesnt all stay on the big streets...... also, and i feel this is a very important point, The heads, ceo's of these companies should not be rewarded in any way.... It seems when the government bails out these big companies, the ceo's get the big bucks, and everyone else loses everything...their job, insurance,retirement funds,and in turn their homes.... I wouldnt want to see this turn into enron....... The ceo's of these companies can more than pay for the entire bill I dont like the idea of having my grandchild's children's children having to pay for this entire Bush and the republican mess...... Reagan did the same thing in the eighties.... and we were paying the bill for all of those years..... I want to see something positive go to individuals.</body> 
 </post> 
</posts>